people ask me what Dro I use all the
time and I say and I'm going to give uh
Cena credit for this I use a uni system
with a custom desktop
manager and otherwise known as
Mac and everybody's like that's not Unix
I'm like yeah it is it's FreeBSD Unix I
had one commenter say FreeBSD isn't
Unix I'm not even going to justify that
with a
response this is my proof according to
the open group.org this is a register
article recently written at which refers
to a bunch of other stuff this is all my
zcast and I'm not going to put links in
the description because you know how to
Google right you can go read it but let
me read this right here uh the other is
a little more significant to the Wi only
slightly seoa showed up as the newest
entry in open group's registry of Unix
certified products in the fact it has
both number one and two spots because
they are separated entries in the Apple
silicon and apple x86 there's no
particular significance the order but if
Apple continues to pay for the
certification uh at some point the X8
86864 version will fall off the list
when Apple supports it they pay tens of
thousands of dollars I don't know the
exact number maybe this has it to
maintain this this thing that says they
are because the people who give out the
proprietary this is UNIX statement who
sued them in 203 was
it was it 20 2003 I think there's
another link it show there was a huge
lawsuit the Unix the the organization
that says that says what is UNIX who by
the way you can't even read their
specifications unless you pay them money
total total this is the reason Linux
exists because these robber barons are
like you said that that Mac was Unix on
your website hand over the cash and they
sued him they sued him they also sued
sco out of existence which is kind of
funny because sko was famous for suing
everybody else and then they died thank
God oh my God can we I just saw
that we're happy the scope people are
dead and gone so so Apple Mac
whether you like them or not whether you
think they ripped off BSD whether you
think jobs is a horrible person you love
wnac whatever you're opinion on Apple it
is factually inaccurate to say that
Apple Mac is not Unix in fact it is the
largest according to the people who own
the Linux
trademark Apple Mac is the largest Unix
distribut
on planet Earth I'm done
[Music]